Today, I'm going to be interviewing one
of the richest 24-year-olds in the entire world,
and his name, who am I here with today?
Aiden Ross.
How did you get rich?
I've made millions of dollars off of just live streaming.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Well, how about you take a guess?
$30 million.
A little bit more.
So today, I flew out here to
Miami at his newly bought $25 million mansion,
the most expensive house in the
county that we're standing in right now,
to ask him one question.
How can somebody become
a multi-millionaire in today's world?
Guys, there's three really golden rules.
And listen, number one is the most emphasized one.
This video is about to be insane,
so stay tuned from start to finish.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
All right, you guys, so we're going to
be linking up with Aiden Ross very shortly.
But before we do that, I'm about to head into
the area where the wealthiest people in Miami hang out,
the design district.
And I'm going to be cold
approaching multi-millionaires and billionaires out there
to figure out how they built their wealth
and how you can do the exact same thing.
Excuse me, sir.
How did you get rich?
Real quick, I have the biggest business media
channel in the world with 15 million followers.
I've interviewed Tom Cruise, Mark Cuban.
Can I get one minute with you real quick?
It's for the younger generation.
I'll show you the channel right here, real quick.
Right here, right here.
That's great.
So how did you get rich?
What industry were you in?
I was in real estate and banking.
In banking, so the finance side of real estate.
Yeah, but I got out
of banking a long time ago.
Why is that?
Just because the environment changed so much.
So mostly real estate.
Development, brokering?
Development.
Here in Miami or where?
No, in Midwest.
In the Midwest, why?
Because I was born there.
And I used to come down here to Florida
whenever the weather would get too cold up there.
Are you still building right now?
No.
I'm retired.
You made your money?
I'm done.
I've monetized everything.
I'm out.
In one year, what was the biggest year you had?
Middle eight figures.
So 50 mil.
You know, middle could be
anywhere from somewhere to somewhere.
What's the best financial advice
you ever got throughout your career?
When you make a sale, wrap it up.
Don't talk past the sale.
Why is that so important?
Well, think about it.
If, let's say, a guy comes in
and wants to buy shoes from you.
And he has his mind
set on a pair of shoes.
And you see him and he
wants to spend money with you, right?
But yet, you then show
him five other pairs of shoes.
And then he gets so confused, he just walks out.
Doesn't buy any.
Nobody talks about that.
When you make a sale, wrap it up.
Real quick, real quick.
I need like two or three more with you.
Give me your best negotiation advice.
Don't negotiate against yourself.
What do you mean?
Meaning that let the guy tell you
what he wants to do rather than...
God gave you two ears
and one mouth for a reason.
You need to listen.
Twice as much listening as you do talk.
What was the lowest point
in your career as an entrepreneur?
I would say I was 21 years
old and I had moved to California.
I had saved up all my
money during high school and college.
I'd saved some money up.
And I graduated from college
and I moved out to California
to pursue a career in residential real estate finance.
And it was commissions only.
And I would say after about three months,
I ran out of money living in California.
You went broke.
I did.
And I came home on a red-eye that
my dad bought me a ticket back to Miami.
I came into the house that morning and
he looked at me and he handed me
what was the equivalent of
like $1,000 back then and said,
get back out there.
There's nothing for you here.
Get your ass back out there.
Were you ever afraid of competition?
Never.
Why not?
Because that's just the way our system works.
Our system works on that basis.
I was an athlete as a kid, so I
always competed and I was never afraid of somebody.
Were you a good salesman?
I hated sales, but I had to do it.
So I guess so.
Give me one more nugget about
sales that's not taught in school.
I would say there's two things.
It's statistical.
So the more people you see, the more
chances you will have at making a sale.
And I have a very close
friend of mine who's in insurance sales.
See the guy, ask him to buy.
That's good.
Come on.
I appreciate you, man.
That was some beautiful advice.
James Dumoulin, sir.
Last nugget for the younger generation.
One more message for them.
Last nugget.
I know you got to get out of here.
Give me one more lesson for the younger generation.
If you're young and you start making
money, keep your hands out of your pockets.
Hey, sir, you got amazing advice.
Thank you for your time.
I appreciate you, man.
Hey, my guy just dropped so much game right there.
My man made $50 million in a single year.
And what do you say?
You see the guy, ask him to buy, man.
A close about, doesn't get paid.
Great interview out here in Miami, man.
Let's keep this one rolling.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
I don't want to talk to him.
I saw your YouTube.
They're great.
I manage $1.2 billion, but
I don't have a family office.
So the bottom line is
great job with everything you're doing.
Did you know I was
going to come up to you?
No, no, no, no.
I never seen you before except from YouTube.
But they saw you on the Bruegelo Cucinini store.
Yeah.
And basically they made a
good comment and stuff like that.
So real quick, what is the
hardest part about managing other people's money?
It's difficult.
You have to do a
good job and stuff like that.
And basically you have to, I'm from Lugano, Switzerland.
So I speak Italian.
You have to use a different type of techniques.
Like in the last two months where
they obviously the market was down 20%.
And they have to obviously try
to offset the instability of the market.
Up to December 2024 was incredible.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No, I didn't come.
No, actually I came with money,
but not a lot of money.
How much did you come here with?
A few million dollars.
So I didn't start from scratch, absolutely.
How did you work up to a billion dollars?
Basically, we attract a lot.
We attract a lot of high network people.
They are very successful in what they do.
They trust us because...
How do you attract the rich people though?
Like how do you get their trust?
We know a lot of people.
How do you build those relationships?
Because when you're born and you go
to private schools and stuff like that,
you're born in a certain circle.
You know these people automatically.
So you got to become friends with rich people?
No, you're already friends because
you go to the same school.
But let's talk to somebody who
doesn't come from a rich family.
Determination, determination, focus, determination
and stuff like that.
What's the best advice you ever got throughout your career?
Never give up.
When I negotiate, people tell me that I destroy people
because...
Because I usually suck oxygen from the room
and the people gasping for air and stuff like that.
You have to use a lot
of time and lengthy type of techniques
to negotiate to your best and stuff like that.
Now you're managing people's money.
Where are you putting that money?
Right now, gold is doing very well.
You like gold?
Yeah, until it lasts.
Right now, it's like $3,500, $3,500.
So let's say in the next six months,
what's the best industry you
should be looking to get into?
Edge funds, indexes and try to protect your investment.
Right now, because I follow Warren
Buffett, I think he's a genius.
I have lots of money in
cash that is not making money
except for 3-4% that I'm making.
Like money market and stuff like that.
So you have a lot
of money in cash right now?
Lots of money in cash.
Because basically the uncertainty of
the time and stuff like that.
Warren Buffett liquidated about $396
billion right now in cash.
And there's a reason.
Because he knew back six
months ago the recession was coming
and because of that, he protected himself with that.
Now it's time, I would
think, in two or three months
to buy and buy at a better price.
What are you going to buy?
Anything that I like very much.
The stocks that Warren Buffett likes.
What industry are the stocks in?
Let's say I've got some cash put to the side.
Where would I put that money to make that work?
It depends.
On the amount of money.
Okay, I have $100,000.
$100,000, I would say a mutual fund.
You like real estate?
We like also real estate a lot.
What type of real estate?
Multi-family or commercial?
No, no, single family.
I live in Coral Gables and
basically we have done incredibly well
buying there, holding, and now the price is like...
So you think very long-term when you make an investment.
You don't look to make quick money at all.
The way you invest money in the stock market,
you can be also a day trader, okay?
But I'm talking about in
the way you do real estate.
We have property in Europe that's like from 1960
and we still own them
because we pay for it.
It's like $3,000, $4,000 at the time
and now they're worth thousands of thousands of dollars,
not millions.
So the return on investment is stellar.
It's incredible.
Let me ask you this.
You're managing money for a lot of very wealthy people,
for billionaires.
What do billionaires do differently from everybody else?
She always criticizes me because she says I go around
looking like a slob.
My wife, my wife.
To make fun of me, she said,
why with all the nice clothes that you have
you go around looking like a slob?
Because I can.
So that's exactly what the
guy from Shark Tank would say.
Robert Herjavec.
Exactly.
And this is something that you're sure about yourself.
You don't have to basically wear...
For example,
I have 40 watches in my collection
and I'm wearing a watch from a friend of mine
who's a micro-brand
that is very cheap compared to all the watches
that I have in a safe deposit box.
I don't wear Rolexes anymore
because right now Rolexes are
used by a lot of people.
It was not exclusive like in 1970.
And that's it.
My wife said,
why do you have all
these nice clothes in the closet
if you don't wear them?
And that's it.
You're not trying to impress anybody else.
No, no, no, no, no.
Because when you have good connection,
you don't impress.
And I go like this everywhere I want to.
That's what's ridiculous about the situation.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Listen, thank you very much.
With a pledge of congratulation on everything.
Thank you, sir. Have a great day.
Guys, this Miami video just
got off to a crazy start
and we're going to be linking
up with Aiden Ross very soon.
But I got to make one thing very clear.
You want to know one thing that I've learned
from interviewing billionaires?
It's that the most successful people,
the richest people are crystal clear communicators.
Understand that if you can't communicate clearly,
you will never close a big deal.
Whether you're pitching investors
or closing eight figure deal,
words matter.
That's why I use Grammarly Pro.
I'm constantly sending emails,
pitching guests,
pitching these multi-millionaire,
multi-billionaire,
these celebrities
and having to plan these shoots.
And Grammarly helps me sound
sure and clear.
Sharp, fast and confident every single time.
There's no more overthinking every sentence.
No more rewrites that take hours.
And Grammarly works exactly where I work
in Gmail, Slack, Notion and more.
Unlike other tools,
there's no copy and paste.
It's just seamless.
And it writes in my voice.
It understands my goals
and it adapts based on who I'm talking to,
whether it's a CEO or just a cold pitch.
And the pro version is a game changer, you guys.
You can instantly adjust the tone
and clarity in the sidebar.
You can set goals to match your style and context.
And you can rewrite anything in just one click
or tweak the settings.
You can even change the
AI prompts to make it yours.
So waste no more time
and level up your productivity right now with Grammarly Pro.
All you have to do is go down
and click the link in the description
or use my link,
grammarly.com
slash hardknock06.
With that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
All right, you guys,
the time has now come.
We are at Aiden Ross's mansion out here.
Guys, I want you to understand
this is the most expensive house in this entire county.
And he bought it for over $25 million.
So I'm going to be linking up with him
to figure out how you can become Aiden Ross rich
in today's world
and what he did to become so successful.
Let's go meet up with him right now.
You guys, come on.
All right, you guys,
I want you to see this right now.
This entire thing is his house.
You could put 10 houses right here, you guys.
I don't even know how many
acres of land this man owns.
But it's safe to say
he lives on an absolute compound out here, you guys.
Come on.
Is this crazy or what?
Oh, yeah.
Excuse me, sir.
Is this your house?
Let's go learn how to use it.
My man.
This is my house.
Hey, this place is incredible, man.
It's great to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you, man.
I'm a big fan of what you got going on,
everything in this channel,
inspiring people,
and I'm proud of myself.
So I just want to give you your flowers.
You're amazing.
You guys are absolutely amazing.
I appreciate that, man.
It means a lot.
Thank you.
Thank you for having us out, man.
I mean, the place is incredible.
Glad you like it.
We're going to drop some
gems for the young guys today
to figure out how they
can get a $25 million house.
Let's go.
Let's go through it.
Let's do it.
You want to make it happen?
Got to make it happen.
Who am I here with today?
My name is Aiden Ross.
Nice to meet you guys watching.
For those who don't know,
how did you make your millions?
I made my millions playing video games
for a very long time,
which is what streaming is today.
Did you have anybody that doubted you early on?
Oh, my own family.
My own family used to doubt me.
I remember my parents were very
big on me going to school,
becoming a lawyer and accountant or something,
something of mine, like with a suit and tie.
But yeah, you know, everyone.
My father actually believed me very early
when my internet was getting declined.
When I was younger to get the best streaming internet,
I just remember that he was always there
to swipe his card and help
me out when I needed it.
So my dad always believed in it.
He would get complaint from the neighbors
and all this stuff.
And he's still the same as
he was five, six years ago
when I came up.
Have you ever been fucked over in business?
All the time.
I think that's what most people,
until you finally know your self-worth
and what you bring to the table.
And I think that if
you can remember who you are
and have your self-worth to
the highest it can possibly be,
I think it prevents you from that.
Because once you realize that you're the main character
in your life, once you protect yourself,
and once you learn kind of all the,
how everyone out in this industry has no heart,
that's when you kind of can learn
how to play that game as well.
Now, you've been at the table with some heavy hitters
closing massive multi-million dollar deals.
What's your best negotiation advice for anybody in business?
The best negotiation advice for anyone in business
is not being scared to walk away.
You know, when you kind of drop that fear
and it's more like,
it's either this happens my way or we walk away.
I think that'll definitely help.
Realize that very early
because a lot of people bluff in business.
I mean, it's just what you do.
It's a business game, it's politics.
You gotta kind of be fake and play both sides.
The person with the most leverage
is the one most willing to walk away.
Did you walk away from a lot of money?
Of course.
I've missed out on several million dollar opportunities
involving deals and involving my
own stuff that I've created.
But hey, for what you may miss,
there's gonna be a whole other path
you've never even seen before.
Now I'm getting brand deals, offers,
all types of business conversations that I've never had.
And it's all from kind of
standing your ground and being you
and just not changing up for anyone but yourself.
So throughout your career,
what was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
Ooh, I don't know.
What does Google say?
What is...
I think there was this point
where everyone was throwing around
these big, big numbers, streaming deals.
But what I've known, which
is worth more, is taking equity.
So I've actually...
My best year, I'll say it's...
Well, how about you take a guess?
$30 million.
You're right around there.
That's a good estimate.
$30 million.
That was pretty good, actually.
Was it actually?
Ah, that's right around there.
Would you say it's a little
bit more or a little bit less?
A little bit more.
A little bit more?
But you're close.
That's incredible, man.
How does that feel?
How old are you?
You're 24 years old making $30 million in a year.
I mean, there's no words
for it except God is amazing.
I'm nobody without the people that
watch me on a daily basis.
They are not only my followers, they're my family members.
I could speak about anything.
And that's what also it comes in what I do.
Building a very loyal fan base that
loves and rise for me no matter what.
And they're the reason why I
can make 30Ms plus a year.
Thank you, guys.
That's a beautiful answer.
One of my favorite business sayings of all time is,
where attention goes, revenue flows.
You did that better than just about anybody else.
How did you build Raving Fans?
You know, I interviewed Ryan Serhant,
one of the biggest real estate brokers in
the entire world out of New York City.
He's selling $4 billion a year.
And he said he used to think the skill set
used to be your ability to sell and all that.
But it's not.
It's the person who gets attention.
What did you do differently from 99% of other people
to be able to make
$30 million in a single year?
I think not fearing.
That's another thing too.
People are very, very hesitant and they fear.
What's the point of being fear?
The reason why I bought
this house right here, everyone's seeing.
I bought this house because
life's about pulling the trigger.
Life's about having no fear.
And if there's consequences, you deal with them after.
You got to pull the trigger
or else somebody's going to pull it.
From 1% to the 99%.
Close mouth doesn't get fed.
That's it.
Pull the trigger and life.
Go buy.
Go do this that you're hesitant.
Oh, should I do this?
Just do it.
If there's consequences, if it was wrong, you learn.
You got to learn things in this world.
You know, nothing's going to
kind of be taught to you.
You got to go out and experience it.
Now, if I'm not mistaken, this
is like the most expensive house.
How much did you buy this house for?
$25,500, I think it says on the website.
$25 million.
Yeah, $25 million.
This is the most expensive house in the city.
Correct.
You know, this is not the beginning.
What I want to do, I want
to buy way more around this area
and kind of build a little empire in a way.
I want to have my family.
I want to have a
bunch of cool stuff to do.
I was telling them you could
put 10 houses in your front yard.
There you go.
All my family can move in, all this stuff.
So I want to expand more.
I want to build more.
So let me ask you this.
They say it's easy to make a lot of money.
It's hard to keep a lot of money.
I agree.
How are you making your money work for you?
I've invested heavily into the crypto
market, which is, by the way,
that's another thing I'm going to talk about.
But I've invested in crypto, real estate, watches.
Cars are a horrible investment.
Doesn't count, obviously, unless it's Porsche.
But yeah, I would say stocks, real estate, crypto.
My story with crypto is you never want
to hold too long in a market, right?
Like, don't get greedy.
That's one thing I did learn this year.
Take your profits when you're up.
Don't get greedy and go for like a 10x.
If you were happy with
a 1.5x or 2x, take it.
Don't get greedy.
The market's always going to be up and down.
It's a game.
You always want cash ready
when the market's ready to drop.
So I think not making that mistake
is something I want to be heavily about.
Sorry, what was the question?
How can somebody get rich
with the money that they have?
Chasing what fear is in the market.
Look what's going on the market, right?
I'm very big into crypto.
Like I said, pull your
profits out when you need to.
But something that's very, very safe.
Again, I'm not a financial
advisor, but Bitcoin, it's just holding.
It's holding itself.
I just feel like putting your money into
something that is going to go up and down,
have a couple drops and up into the year.
That's kind of what you want to
do with your money, in my opinion.
Play hard.
You got to be competitive.
But again, don't do what I do.
Take your profits.
It's very important to take your profits.
I want to challenge you.
What's the best advice you've gotten throughout your career?
I've actually learned this very, very recently.
The best piece of advice you can
give to somebody is to not take advice.
And what I mean is when you're growing
up and you learn things as a child,
and when you develop and you become
who you are by growing up and experiencing,
whether it's trauma or good life experiences,
I think when you tell someone,
don't do this, don't do that,
majority of people that are the entrepreneur type,
they want to do what the
opposite crowd is telling them to.
Everyone's saying, Aiden, go to school, go to school.
If I were to take their
advice, I wouldn't be where I'm at.
And I'm not saying going to school is wrong.
I'm just saying everybody has their own paths.
Everybody knows what they're supposed
to do with their own life.
And that's why nobody should really give
heavy advice on what somebody wants to do
or how somebody else should run their life.
It's your life. Take your own advice.
You can learn. You can have input.
But learn by your own mistakes and
learn by your own successful points as well.
We just interviewed Will Smith.
Huge.
He was telling us that
you get to a certain level,
it's like not many people
that you can take advice from.
It's like, I wouldn't have done none of
what you did, but look at what you accomplished.
100%. And that's what it's about, right?
That's why I love this page. What you
guys all have going on, this is amazing.
Because when I'm in bed and I just
see this, I just see these hungry people,
it's really, really good what you guys are doing.
Because pages like this, when I see a TikTok,
whether it's Shaq or whether I
see whoever you guys have on,
I saw the Ruben one.
That's actually what made me hit you guys
off because Ruben's a good friend of mine.
But it's just super motivating
seeing other people in my space.
And I'm sure to the followers' end as well,
I mean, it's just amazing seeing people create.
We're all humans. We all
have fingers. We all have legs.
We all have arms. We
all have noses, mouths, et cetera.
We're all the same. Everyone can
kind of do anything in this world.
You just have to put your mind to it.
You'll be called crazy at first,
but then you'll be called
a genius when you accomplish it.
You've lost everything tomorrow. Could you make it all back?
Yeah, I would. And here's how I would do it.
In my space, when it
comes to content creation, short form,
whether it's clipping, shorts, whatever it is,
I would find a way to
where I can start doing IRL streaming,
build my way back up
and doing a bunch of stuff
and having them all ready to
go in clips and stuff like that.
Besides the actual streaming part of things,
I would just make sure my mentality was
never just worried about what I'm going to do.
You kind of just have to wake up every
day and just kind of want to do without anxiety.
You've got to have your overconfidence in this world.
And I think that would help me get
to where I'm at a lot sooner as well.
Because I feel like when you're coming up,
you really do have to
have the ultimate confidence in myself.
In the beginning, I had a very bad anxiety.
How did you ultimately find that self-belief
to go make tens of millions of dollars?
Self-belief just comes from literally just having no plan B.
And I know it sounds crazy, and
I just never had a plan B.
It was always just I had to wake
up. Whether I felt anxious or felt like shit,
I had to wake up and
do what I had to do.
What part?
What's it like to say that believing that you
can is more profitable than believing that you can't?
Exactly, 100%. You got to just believe.
It might sound crazy, like I said,
but then when you accomplish it, whether
you get to where you need to get,
you'll be a genius. And
that's just how the world works.
So you mentioned a little bit earlier,
I want to tap back
into you talked about having equity.
How important has ownership been for you?
Oh, I have ownership for one
of the biggest streaming platforms, Kik.
And it's amazing. I mean, when you have equity,
it's kind of like it doesn't
really necessarily matter about the quick cash.
You could build up a company that could sell
for billions of dollars like I am with Kik.
And my percent will be worth
a lot of money one day.
When it comes to equity, that's the real control.
That's the real wealth.
It's very cool to take these
cash deals in the beginning, 100%,
but I think as you come up in business,
learning equity is the strongest thing you
can get out of any type of deal.
Ownership is king. Ownership is king.
I want to tap back in one
more time about like the content creation ultimately.
You were talking about like the clipping.
Give me that blueprint that it takes, right?
If you were to start over today
and you had to blow up again
to be able to build a multi eight-figure a year,
you know, business essentially from the content creation,
what would that be? For the people
that may not understand what clipping means exactly,
our audience can be a little
bit older, 30 to 50. I understand.
Let's break that down to them.
Make it real simple for them.
So clipping is pretty much
a form of content where you make
a clip out of a big moment.
So for example, if I were to
go do a live stream swimming with sharks,
so that live stream itself
will probably be about two hours,
but the clip itself could be
anywhere from like 10 to 30 seconds,
which will make a viral moment,
which will funnel people to where
you're actually live streaming off of.
So pretty much clipping is just
a funnel to your main live stream,
if that makes sense. So a lot
of people will kind of question and ask,
how do streamers even make money? Like
how do you make money live streaming?
How have you made tens
of millions of dollars live streaming?
Depending on what platform you're on,
you can earn money streaming by subscriptions,
which you pay to not see advertisements
on certain platforms. You could donate to
the streamer to just to donate extras,
like a tip, which is also very
good and it adds up a lot.
And then KCIP, which is partner income program.
I'm gonna show you how much money
I make in 15 or 16 streams.
I'm pulled up right now. But how Kik does
my platform is we pay you based off the hour.
So let's say you averaged 100 viewers.
You can make seven, eight bucks an hour.
If you average a thousand viewers, you can make hundred,
two hundred bucks an hour just streaming on Kik.
Let me just show you
what the partner income looks like.
So in the month of June, as you
can see, I've done 18 streams and made $623,000.
That's not including whatever else I have going on.
But I could show you too. So
this is June. Total paid streams 18, $623,000.
In June. In June alone. If I stream
30 days, I can make way more. It's huge.
And your last message to the younger generation.
How can somebody become
a multi-millionaire in today's world?
They want to get Aiden Ross rich
in today's world. How can they get wealthy?
Guys, there's three, there's three really golden rules.
And listen, number one is the most emphasized one.
Remember guys, it takes a lot
of luck to become a streamer.
I've been doing it for a long time, a
long time before anyone really knew who I was.
On and off for 10 years. But
my message to you guys is please,
you might sound crazy at the
beginning of whatever you got going on,
but I promise you, and I
emphasize this, when you make it,
when you make it for yourself in
this world, it's going to feel amazing.
And you're not going to be crazy anymore.
You'll be called a genius by
your peers and your family, et cetera.
Just please believe in yourself as well.
Number one, right now, focus on something for a year.
You could be working at the same
time. You could be working a regular job,
but focus on something for a year.
When you're not working, you're doing this.
And I guarantee you'll see results
in whatever you guys have going on.
And it's best of luck to you guys.
I pray I get to meet all of you.
And I pray that all of you
guys can make big purchases like this.
I know you all can. Manifestation is so real.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
I need you guys to like
and subscribe for amazing content every week
because nobody else is doing this, you guys.
We just interviewed one of the
most renowned streamers in the entire world,
one of the biggest content
creators on the planet, Aiden Ross.
Guys, like, subscribe. And if you
are not a member yet, guys,
go down and click the link
in the description of this video
to join the number one community
for business owners in the entire world.
It's the School of Mentors,
and I give you direct access
to the multimillionaires and billionaires I
interview every week here on this channel.
Only at the School of Hard Knocks.
I can't wait to see
you guys in the next video.